# **Bianchi Maximiliano**

Front-end Developer

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina (UTC-3) (+54) 9 3416080747 maxi bianchi@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/maximiliano-bianchi1/

Front-end Developer with 5 years of experience and 6 years in the IT Sector with a technological stack in Javascrypt(React, AngularJS, Typescript), MySQL, NodeJs, Jira, Bitbucket, Git, Github, AzureDevops. I have worked in the field of consulting providing support to strategic clients in the private sector. I am always in constant search of new opportunities for me to expand my knowledge in new technologies and projects that allow me to grow professionally.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## TORC LLC, Front-end Developer - July, 2023 - current position

- Correcting hotfixes, issues and new code requirements in front-end torc's applications in various pages.
- Implementing new design in code for specific jobs page, adding new content, fields, validations, images, among others to translate the design created previously in figma to the front-end application.
- Testing and making reports of every implementation made to keep record of the changes.

Technological stack: HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, Javascript (Jquery), React.js, PHP, Git, Github, Visual Studio Code, Graphql.

#### ACCENTURE SRL, QA Automation Eng Analyst project #2 - Internal Accenture Application - December, 2020 - July 2023

- The user experience was improved by 80% by implementing accessibility tools within the front-end.
- The user experience was improved by 50% by creating validations in several of the forms presented by the software to help the user identify the necessary data to complete.
- Software quality tests were optimized by 50% with the implementation of their automation.

<u>Technological stack:</u> Web software with Javascrypt (AngularJS, Typescript), SQL (postgresql), NodeJs VisualStudio, Git and AzureDevops.

## ACCENTURE SRL, QA Automation Eng Analyst project #1 - Technical Internet Application - December, 2020 - July 2023

- Software options were optimized by 30% by implementing a new workflow without quality.
- A flow was generated to be able to complete the tasks without an internet connection. 10% impact on the entire application. Keep the database updated and with what is necessary with the automation of deleting the record with a time greater than 30 days.
- The possibilities of registering repairs have been increased by 10% by adding the corresponding antenna models.

<u>Technological stack:</u> Mobile App with HTML5, CSS3, Javascrypt (JQuery), PHP (laravel, composer), VisualStudioCode, MySQL (Workbench) Git, Postman, Bitbucket.

#### CODEV, Full Stack Developer - march, 2018 - December 2020

- Software improvements of 80% were implemented, the layout and functionality of the front-end was developed for various e-commerce, so that the products and services available to each client can be viewed on the web domain. This generated that the user can select a product and then make the purchase of it.
- An impact of 50% was created through the implementation of a style sheet to improve the user's experience when viewing the information and so that the messages and intentions that the company has proposed can be transmitted.
- Review and creation of a relational database together with the subsequent integration of services and validations with an API-REST to be able to connect them with the front-end. An improvement of 40% since it allowed manual testing of the services through tools such as postman.

<u>Technological stack:</u> Ecommerce with HTML5, CSS3, Javascrypt (JQuery), PHP (laravel, composer), VisualStudioCode, MySQL (Workbench) Git, Postman, Bitbucket.

## **PROJECTS**

# Reciclados de caucho - www.recicldadosdecaucho.com

• Website development with wordpress for ecommerce where they can sell their products and services.

Radioactivarosario- www.radioactivarosario.com

• Construction of a website with wordpress for radio-online where they can sell their products and services.

**UDEMY**– application uploaded to GitHub.

• Web-app with AngularJs 9, Bootstrap and nodejs. Development of a physical training app with routines and record personal progress.

## **SKILLS**

Programming languages: Advanced: HTML5, CSS3, Javascrypt, PHP; Intermediate: React; Basic: NodeJs, React-Native, and VueJs.

Frameworks: Advanced: Jquery, Laravel, Composer; Intermediate: AngularJs, Typescript, Mootols; Basic: Firebase, Sympony and Tailwind.

**Databases:** Advanced: MySQL; Intermediate: SQL; Basic: XML.

**Collaborative tools:** Git, Jira, Bitbucket, Trello, Slack, AzureDevops and Github.

**Agile:** sprints, daily's, retrospectivas, planning. **Languages:** Fluid: English; Native: Spanish.

# **EDUCATION**

Brigadier Lopez Institute - Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina. Informatics Engineering, December of 2020.

Architecture, Planning and Design College -Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina. Architect, 4 year of career.

**San Bartolome School** – Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina. Bachelor's Degree in English.

San Bartolome School -Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina. DELF Junior Degree.

## **CERTIFICATES**

**EF SET CERTIFICATE** – Standart English Test, July 2020.

**Udemy** – Certificate Javascript and Jquery, April 2021.

**Udemy** – Certificate Typescript, November 2021.

**Udemy** – Certificate React and Firebase, November 2021.

**Udemy** – Certificate VueJs and Firebase, November 2021.

**Udemy** – Certificate Concepts programming, July 2021.